Antonio Coronado

{ tonydevmx@gmail.com | {+52} 4811560888 | Artstation | Portfolio }

EDUCATION

UASLP

Universidad Autónoma de San Luis Potosí

MECHATRONIC ENGINEERING 08/2013 - 09/2018

UVEG

Universidad del Estado de Guanajuato

COMPUTATIONAL SYSTEMS

Engineering

08/2020 - 12/2021

UPSRJ

Universidad Politécnica de Santa Rosa de Jáuregui

Animation and Visual Effects

ENGINEERING

01/2019 - 02/2022

LINKS

Webpage://tonycoronado.github.io Github://tonycoronado LinkedIn://antcor

EXTRA ABILITIES

Familiar with:

- HTML CSS Perforce Slack
- Trello Monday.com HacknPlan Tools I use:
- Visual Studio Code Visual Studio Community

ENGLISH

ITEP CERTIFICATE

Level: C1 Advanced

COURSES

COMPLETED

- Codecademy web Development with HTML and CSS
- Teamtreehouse C# Basics and game development

IN PROCESS

- Harvard's CS50
- CG Spectrum Game Design Course
- Tom Looman's Unreal C++ Course

SUMMARY

Game Developer with 2 years of experience working with Unreal Engine on 5 Indie projects using blueprints. I am used to work as solo developer and with teams up to 15 people. Passionate about videogames and highly self-taught person.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Skilled with:

- Unreal Engine 4 / Unreal Engine 5
- Blueprints scripting language
- Creating, testing and simulating assets functionality.

Familiar with:

- Maya Photoshop Substance 3D Painter
- Blender C++ Syntax C Syntax OOP
- Creating In-editor tools

Soft Skills:

• Problem solving mindset • Strong commitment • Communication

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

UE5 Game Developer - Studio Gyris 03/2022 - 09/2022

- Created an in-editor tool to apply custom LODs to more than 400 assets simultaneously, improving 8-10 FPS in-game with only a couple of clicks.
- Implemented destruction features with blueprints to multiple assets.
- Devised, created and implemented a spawn system to randomize obstacles at the track making the game way more dynamic.

UE4 Game Developer - Ackitash Gaming

05/2021 - 03/2022

- Solved dozens of errors in blueprints.
- Planned and implemented systems and game mechanics using blueprints.
- Programmed with blueprints a MVP of 10 min playable with one main quest, minimal level design and various mechanics.

UE4 Game Developer - Jomas Rage

09/2021 - 02/2022

- Created a prototype with combat mechanics using multiple melee weapons with blueprints.
- Made an In-editor tool with blueprints to randomize the rotation of multiple assets placed in the viewport.
- Programmed an inventory system with blueprints.
- Created zombies AI behaviour with blueprints.

3D Artist - Jutsu Online

12/2020 - 09/2021

• Designed a City with 50 buildings in Maya for a MMORPG Naruto themed game using Maya and Substance Painter.

EXTRA PRO JECTS

Twimbler A copy of Twitter using HTML and CSS